Bendix, Reinhard; Papers ger021
M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections & Archives
- Published and Unpublished Writings by Others, 5; 128 file folders
  - Habermas, Jürgen. "Paper for a conference on the occasion of the 50th Anniversary of the University in Exile, Berlin, Dec. 7, 1984", Undated; typescript, clippings (Box 11 (5-Published and Unpublished Writings by Others), Folder 33)
  - Harper, Edward B., Undated; reprints (Box 11 (5-Published and Unpublished Writings by Others), Folder 34)
  - Hartmann, Heinz, Undated; reprint (Box 11 (5-Published and Unpublished Writings by Others), Folder 35)
  - Hechter, Michael. "Review Essay. The Modern World-System: Capitalist Agriculture and the Origins of the European World-Economy in the Sixteenth Century by Immanuel Wallerstein", 1975 May; typescript (Box 11 (5-Published and Unpublished Writings by Others), Folder 36)
  - Hennis, Wilhelm. "Spuren Nietzsches im Werk Max Webers", 1985 September 27; typescript, reprint, clippings (Box 11 (5-Published and Unpublished Writings by Others), Folder 37)
  - Hermassi, Elbaki. "Patterns of Research on the Third World", Undated; typescript (Box 11 (5-Published and Unpublished Writings by Others), Folder 38)
  - Hirschman, Albert O., Undated; reprint (Box 11 (5-Published and Unpublished Writings by Others), Folder 39)
  - Hoselitz, Bert F. "Advanced and Underdeveloped Countries. A Study in Development Contrasts", Undated; typescript, reprint (Box 11 (5-Published and Unpublished Writings by Others), Folder 40)
  - Hsiao, Gene T. "The Background and Development of 'The Proletarian Cultural Revolution'", 1966; mimeograph (Box 11 (5-Published and Unpublished Writings by Others), Folder 41)
  - Huckarde, Heinrich.Lieder der Einsamkeit, 1908; photocopy (Box 11 (5-Published and Unpublished Writings by Others), Folder 42)
  - Janowitz, Morris. "Political Sociology", 1965 October; mimeograph (Box 11 (5-Published and Unpublished Writings by Others), Folder 43)
  - Jonas, Hans, Undated; reprints (Box 11 (5-Published and Unpublished Writings by Others), Folder 44)
  - Jowitt, Ken. "Soviet Neotraditionalism: The Political Corruption of a Leninist Regime", 1982; mimeograph (Box 11 (5-Published and Unpublished Writings by Others), Folder 45)
  - Kannappan, Subbiah. "A Preliminary Bibliography on the Labour Problem in Indian Economic Development", 1955 June; bound mimeographed typescript (Box 11 (5-Published and Unpublished Writings by Others), Folder 46)
  - Kaplan, Norman, Undated; reprints (Box 11 (5-Published and Unpublished Writings by Others), Folder 47)
  - Karve, D.D. "The Linguistic Problem in India", 1960 February 8; mimeograph (Box 11 (5-Published and Unpublished Writings by Others), Folder 48)
  - Keasbey, William. "Recent Trends in the Role of the Soviet Manager". M.A. thesis, ca. 1955 (Box 11 (5-Published and Unpublished Writings by Others), Folder 49)
  - Knutson, Andie L., Undated; reprints (Box 11 (5-Published and Unpublished Writings by Others), Folder 50)
  - Köhler, Wolfgang. "Psychologie des inneren Verhaltens", 1931; typescript (carbon) (Box 11 (5-Published and Unpublished Writings by Others), Folder 51)
  - Kothari, Rajni, Undated (Box 11 (5-Published and Unpublished Writings by Others), Folder 52)
    "Implications of Nation-Building for the Typology of Political Systems". Mimeo., Sept. 18-23, 1967; "Processes of Political Modernisation". Mimeo., Sept. 18-23, 1967; reprints; clippings.
  - Krockow, Christian Graf von. "Incertitudes Allemandes. Betrachtungen aus Anlaß der deutschen Studentenunruhen", Undated; mimeograph (Box 11 (5-Published and Unpublished Writings by Others), Folder 53)
  - Kurland, Philip B., Undated; reprint (Box 11 (5-Published and Unpublished Writings by Others), Folder 54)
  - Kvistad, Gregg O. with Christine Schoefer. "Between State and Society. Green Political Ideology in the Mid-Eighties", Undated; typescript (Box 11 (5-Published and Unpublished Writings by Others), Folder 55)
  - LaPorte, Todd. "On the Matter of Ethics and Values in (or for) Science and Technology", 1977 January; typescript (Box 11 (5-Published and Unpublished Writings by Others), Folder 56)
  - Lacey, Michael J. "The National Seminary of Learning: Washington Scientists and the Rise of the Modern State in the Late Nineteenth Century", 1982 December 27-1982 December 30; mimeograph (Box 11 (5-Published and Unpublished Writings by Others), Folder 57)
  - Lamb, Helen B. "The 'State' and Economic Development in India", 1952 April 25-1952 April 27; mimeograph (Box 11 (5-Published and Unpublished Writings by Others), Folder 58)
  - Lambert, Richard D. "Factory Workers and the Non-Factory Population in Poona", Undated; mimeograph (Box 11 (5-Published and Unpublished Writings by Others), Folder 59)
  - Lazarsfeld, Paul F. "Some Historical Notes on the Study of Action", Summer 1954; Summer 1957; mimeograph (Box 11 (5-Published and Unpublished Writings by Others), Folder 60)
  - Lepsius, M. Rainer. "Modernisierungspolitik als Institutionenbildung: Kriterien institutioneller Differenzierung", Undated; typescript, photocopy (Box 11 (5-Published and Unpublished Writings by Others), Folder 61)
  - Leys, Wayne A. R. and Charner M. Perry. "Philosophy and the Public Interest", Undated; mimeograph (Box 11 (5-Published and Unpublished Writings by Others), Folder 62)
  - Lipset, Seymour Martin. "Some Personal Notes for a History of the Department of Sociology at Columbia", Undated; typescript, reprints (Box 11 (5-Published and Unpublished Writings by Others), Folder 63)
  - Lockwood, David. "Capitalism and the Welfare State. A Study in the Politics of Industrialization", Undated; typescript (carbon) (Box 11 (5-Published and Unpublished Writings by Others), Folder 64)
  - Malick, Clay P., Undated; reprints (Box 11 (5-Published and Unpublished Writings by Others), Folder 65)
  - Marquardt, Frederick D., Undated; reprint (Box 11 (5-Published and Unpublished Writings by Others), Folder 66)
  - Mayer, Kurt, Undated; reprints (Box 11 (5-Published and Unpublished Writings by Others), Folder 67)
  - Merton, Robert K. "The Expert and Research in Applied Social Science", 1947 November; mimeograph (Box 11 (5-Published and Unpublished Writings by Others), Folder 68)
  - Meuschel, Sigrid "Kulturnation oder Staatsnation? -- Zur Renaissance der Suche nach nationaler Identität in beiden deutschen Staaten", Undated; reprint (Box 11 (5-Published and Unpublished Writings by Others), Folder 69)
  - Miller, Abraham H. and James S. Robbins. "Who Did Vote for Hitler? A Reanalysis of Class and Mass Society theories", 1985 December; typescript, photocopy (Box 11 (5-Published and Unpublished Writings by Others), Folder 70)
  - Mitchell, Arnold. "Marketing the Arts", Undated; mimeograph (Box 11 (5-Published and Unpublished Writings by Others), Folder 71)
  - Moe, Henry Allen. "Statement by Dr. Henry Allen Moe, Chairman, National Endowment for the Humanities", 1966 March 20; mimeograph (Box 11 (5-Published and Unpublished Writings by Others), Folder 72)
  - Mushaben, Joyce M. "Juridicial Precedence Turned Legislative Prescription: The Courts and Higher Education in the Federal Republic and the United States", 1982 March 17-1982 March 20; bound typescript (Box 11 (5-Published and Unpublished Writings by Others), Folder 73)
  - Nelson, Benjamin. "The Future of Illusions", Undated; mimeograph, reprint (Box 11 (5-Published and Unpublished Writings by Others), Folder 74)
  - Noelle-Neumann, Elisabeth. "Wandlungen im Bewusstsein der Arbeiter", Undated; typescript, photocopy (Box 11 (5-Published and Unpublished Writings by Others), Folder 75)
  - Nonet, Philippe. "Organizations as Legal Systems", 1977 April; mimeograph (Box 11 (5-Published and Unpublished Writings by Others), Folder 76)
  - Odaka, Kunio. "Traditionalism and Democracy in Japanese Industry", 1962 September; typescript (carbon) (Box 11 (5-Published and Unpublished Writings by Others), Folder 77)
  - Omvedt, Gail. Chapters of dissertation, Undated; typescript (Box 11 (5-Published and Unpublished Writings by Others), Folder 78)
  - Omvedt, Gail, Undated (Box 11 (5-Published and Unpublished Writings by Others), Folder 79)
    "Caste, Conflict, and Rebellion". M.A. thesis, undated; "The Non-brahman Challenge in Roona: 1922-26". Mimeo., 1972.
  - Ossowski, Stanislaw. "Divergent Aspects of Social Reality", Undated; mimeograph (Box 12 (5-Published and Unpublished Writings by Others), Folder 1)
  - Petersen, William K., Undated (Box 12 (5-Published and Unpublished Writings by Others), Folder 2)
    "Population as a Field of Study". Typescript (carbon), undated; (with Robert E. Kennedy, Jr.); "Nationality, Race, and Religion: Subnations in the World Today". Mimeo., undated.
  - Phillips, Walter. "Technological Levels, Structuring of the Labor Force, and Resistance to Change in the Early Stages of Industrialization", 1960 July 27; mimeograph (Box 12 (5-Published and Unpublished Writings by Others), Folder 3)
  - Powell, Eugene. "Human Nature in Managerial Ideology", Undated; typescript (Box 12 (5-Published and Unpublished Writings by Others), Folder 4)
  - Rapoport, David C. "Generations in America", 1970; mimeograph (Box 12 (5-Published and Unpublished Writings by Others), Folder 5)
  - Rawin, Solomon John. "The Process of Modernization and the Ideology of the Russian Intelligentsia", Undated; typescript (Box 12 (5-Published and Unpublished Writings by Others), Folder 6)
  - Raymond, Robert. "The Development of Various Forms of Organisation of the Work Process and their Role as Non-monetary Incentives for Increasing Labor Productivity in the Soviet Union", Undated; typescript (Box 12 (5-Published and Unpublished Writings by Others), Folder 7)
  - Retzlaff, Ralph H. "A Case Study of Panchayats in a North Indian Village", 1959 February; mimeograph (Box 12 (5-Published and Unpublished Writings by Others), Folder 8)
  - Riesebrodt, Martin, Undated; reprint (Box 12 (5-Published and Unpublished Writings by Others), Folder 9)
  - Riley, Lawrence E. and Elmer A. Spreitzer. "The Presidential Address as Ritual and Reflection. An Analysis of the Presidential Addresses to the American Sociological Association", 1968 August; mimeograph (Box 12 (5-Published and Unpublished Writings by Others), Folder 10)
  - Rodriguez, Javier. "Las categorías de lo historic en la sociología de Max Weber", 1995; reprint (Box 12 (5-Published and Unpublished Writings by Others), Folder 11)
  - Rokkan, Stein. "Approaches to the Study of Political Participation", Undated; mimeograph (Box 12 (5-Published and Unpublished Writings by Others), Folder 12)
  - Rosenstein, Eliezer. Book notes on modernization and equality, Undated; typescript (Box 12 (5-Published and Unpublished Writings by Others), Folder 13)
  - Rossetti, Carlo. "Nation, nationalities and classical sociology", ca. 1986; typescript (Box 12 (5-Published and Unpublished Writings by Others), Folder 14)
  - Roth, Guenther, Undated (Box 12 (5-Published and Unpublished Writings by Others), Folder 15)
    "A Cautionary Tale for the New German Kulturpolitik. Hugo Münsterberg's and Karl Lamprecht's Misadventures in the United States". Mimeo., undated; "Americana: Ein konkreter Kultursoziologischer Beitrag zur Geschichte der deutsch-amerikanischen Beziehungen". Mimeo., undated; "Developmental History in Max Weber's Time and Work". Mimeo., undated.
  - Roth, Guenther, Undated (Box 12 (5-Published and Unpublished Writings by Others), Folder 16)
    "Marx and Weber on the United States -- Today". Typescript, photocopy, undated; "Origins of German Workers Discipline". Typescript, undated; "Partisanship and Scholarship. An Autobiographical Essay". Typescript, photocopy, Dec. 1986.
  - Roth, Guenther, Undated (Box 12 (5-Published and Unpublished Writings by Others), Folder 17)
    "The Past and Future of Historical Sociology". Typescript, photocopy, December 1986; "Political Critiques of Max Weber: Some Implications for Political Sociology". Mimeo., September 1, 1964.
  - Roth, Guenther.Social Democracy in Imperial Germany, Undated (Box 12 (5-Published and Unpublished Writings by Others), Folder 18)
    Contents, mimeo.; text references.
  - Roth, Guenther, Undated; reprints, clippings (Box 12 (5-Published and Unpublished Writings by Others), Folder 19)
  - Rustow, Dankwart A. "The World of Nations: An Essay on Modernization and Political Leadership", ca. 1965; typescript (carbon) (Box 12 (5-Published and Unpublished Writings by Others), Folder 20)
  - Saran, A. K. "Sociology of Knowledge and Traditional Thought", Undated; mimeograph (Box 12 (5-Published and Unpublished Writings by Others), Folder 21)
  - Schluchter, Wolfgang, Undated (Box 12 (5-Published and Unpublished Writings by Others), Folder 22)
    "Rationalismus der Weltbeherrschung. Eine Explikation von Max Webers Gesellschaftsgeschichte". Mimeo., undated; "Überlegungen zur Edition von 'Wirtschaft und Gesellschaft'". Mimeo., January 1986; "Umbildungen des Charismas. Überlegungen zu Max Webers Herrschaftssoziologie". Mimeo., 1985.
  - Schmitter, Philippe C., Undated (Box 12 (5-Published and Unpublished Writings by Others), Folder 23)
    "Draft Proposal for a Joint Committee on Western European Studies". Mimeo., Feb. 1975; "Neo-Corporatism and the State". Bound typescript, May 1984.
  - Schnur, Roman, Undated; reprint (Box 12 (5-Published and Unpublished Writings by Others), Folder 24)
  - Schran, Peter, Undated (Box 12 (5-Published and Unpublished Writings by Others), Folder 25)
    "The Recognition of Political Rights and of Social Rights in various European Countries and in Japan -- a Comparison". Typescript, undated; "Research Report on Managerial Ideologies in Germany in the Late 18th and Early 19th Century". Typescript, undated.
  - Schran, Peter. "Research Report on Changes in the Structure of the German Work Force and Changes in the Structure of the German Enterprises Primarily during the Late Nineteenth and Early Twentieth Centuries", 1957 October; typescript (Box 12 (5-Published and Unpublished Writings by Others), Folder 26)
  - Schran, Peter. "Research Report on Migration and Urbanization in Germany (1840-1910)", Undated; typescript (Box 12 (5-Published and Unpublished Writings by Others), Folder 27)
  - Schudson, Michael. "A Ruminating Retrospective on the Liberal Arts, the Social Sciences, and Social Science 2", 1984; typescript (Box 12 (5-Published and Unpublished Writings by Others), Folder 28)
  - Sciulli, David. "Voluntaristic Action: The Reconstruction of a District Concept", 1985; mimeograph (Box 12 (5-Published and Unpublished Writings by Others), Folder 29)
  - Selznick, Philip, Undated (Box 12 (5-Published and Unpublished Writings by Others), Folder 30)
    "Rejoinder to Wolin". Mimeo., Feb. 1968; (with Gertrude Jaeger Selznick). "The Idea of a Social System". Mimeo., Sept. 4, 1959.
  - Sharma, K. N. "Cultural Preconditions of Development", Undated; mimeograph (Box 12 (5-Published and Unpublished Writings by Others), Folder 31)
  - Shils, Edward A. "The Private University: Its Present and Future", 1968 November; mimeograph (Box 12 (5-Published and Unpublished Writings by Others), Folder 32)
  - Sinha, K. K. "Some Ominous Trends in India", 1957; mimeograph (Box 12 (5-Published and Unpublished Writings by Others), Folder 33)
  - Skocpol, Theda. "Varieties of 'Historical Sociology'", 1977 September 14; mimeograph (Box 12 (5-Published and Unpublished Writings by Others), Folder 34)
  - Soviak, Eugene. "Baba Tatsui and the Role of the Early Meiji Intellectual", 1963 April 17; typescript (Box 12 (5-Published and Unpublished Writings by Others), Folder 35)
  - Srinivas, M. N., Undated; reprints (Box 12 (5-Published and Unpublished Writings by Others), Folder 36)
  - Stark, Rodney. "Graduate Study at Berkeley: An Assessment of Attrition and Duration", Undated; mimeograph (Box 12 (5-Published and Unpublished Writings by Others), Folder 37)
  - Stern, Carola. "Der letzte grosse Umformungsprozess der Sed-Elite auf der Parteihochschule 'Karl Marx' in Kleinmachnow", Undated; typescript, photocopy (Box 12 (5-Published and Unpublished Writings by Others), Folder 38)
  - Stinchcombe, Arthur L., Undated (Box 12 (5-Published and Unpublished Writings by Others), Folder 39)
    "The Philosophy of Academic Authority". Typescript, undated; "Stratification". Mimeo., undated.
  - Trans-Pacific Theory Conference on Modernity and Development. "Discussion by Reinhard Bendix of papers submitted". Also papers by Man-Gap Lee, Takashi Miyajima, Hideichiro Nakano, and Kyong-Dong Kim, Undated (Box 12 (5-Published and Unpublished Writings by Others), Folder 40)
  - Taubes, Jacob, Undated; reprint (Box 12 (5-Published and Unpublished Writings by Others), Folder 41)
  - Trow, Martin, Undated (Box 12 (5-Published and Unpublished Writings by Others), Folder 42)
    "Bell, Book and Berkley: Reflections occasioned by a reading of Daniel Bell's The Reforming of General Education". Mimeo., reprint; "The Public and Private Lives of Higher Education". Typescript, photocopy, Nov. 16, 1973; "Urban Problems and University Problems". Mimeo., Mar. 23-25, 1969.
  - Udy, Stanley H. Jr. "A Memorandum on the Comparative Analysis of Societies", 1967 March; typescript, photocopy (Box 12 (5-Published and Unpublished Writings by Others), Folder 43)
  - Vincent, Clark E., Undated; reprint (Box 12 (5-Published and Unpublished Writings by Others), Folder 44)
  - Wilensky, Harold L., Undated; reprint (Box 12 (5-Published and Unpublished Writings by Others), Folder 45)
  - Wolff, Kurt H. "The Intellectual: Between Culture and Politics", 1971; reprint (Box 12 (5-Published and Unpublished Writings by Others), Folder 46)
  - Wolins, Martin, Undated; reprint (Box 12 (5-Published and Unpublished Writings by Others), Folder 47)
  - Woods, Baldwin M. "The University and its Services to the Professions", 1948 May 3; mimeograph (Box 12 (5-Published and Unpublished Writings by Others), Folder 48)
  - Zelnik, Reginald E. "Passivity and Protest in Germany and Russia: Barrington Moore's Conception of Working-Class Responses to Injustice", Undated; mimeograph (Box 12 (5-Published and Unpublished Writings by Others), Folder 49)
- Miscellaneous Materials, Notes, 6; 26 file folders
  This series consists of folders on various topics, both for courses taught by Bendix as well as topics of research for his publications.
  - Academic Freedom. University of California Loyalty Oath controversy, 1949-1952 (Box 13 (6-Miscellaneous Materials, Notes), Folder 1)
  - Academic Freedom. University of Colorado (Henry Ehrmann), 1952 (Box 13 (6-Miscellaneous Materials, Notes), Folder 2)
  - Academic Freedom, Undated; clippings, printed materials (Box 13 (6-Miscellaneous Materials, Notes), Folder 3)
  - American Association for a Democratic Germany, 1940s (Box 13 (6-Miscellaneous Materials, Notes), Folder 4)
  - Anspach, Ralph. Research notes on German Industrialism, Undated (Box 13 (6-Miscellaneous Materials, Notes), Folder 5)
  - Belief in Science, Undated (Box 13 (6-Miscellaneous Materials, Notes), Folder 6)
  - Book notes, 1940s (Box 13 (6-Miscellaneous Materials, Notes), Folder 7)
  - Book notes, miscellaneous, Undated (Box 13 (6-Miscellaneous Materials, Notes), Folder 8)
  - Bureaucracy. Book excerpts, notes and summaries, bibliographies, Undated (Box 13 (6-Miscellaneous Materials, Notes), Folder 9-10)
  - Civic, Political, and Social Rights: England. List of Acts and Laws, early 1950s (Box 13 (6-Miscellaneous Materials, Notes), Folder 11)
  - Education, Undated (Box 13 (6-Miscellaneous Materials, Notes), Folder 12)
  - Federal Civil Servants. Materials, notes, early 1950s (Box 13 (6-Miscellaneous Materials, Notes), Folder 13)
  - India, 1961-1962 (Box 13 (6-Miscellaneous Materials, Notes), Folder 14)
  - India. Election, 1962 (Box 13 (6-Miscellaneous Materials, Notes), Folder 15)
    Clippings from The Statesman.
  - Japan, 1962 (Box 13 (6-Miscellaneous Materials, Notes), Folder 16)
  - Karl Marx and Marxism, Undated (Box 13 (6-Miscellaneous Materials, Notes), Folder 17)
  - Kisch, Herbert. Book notes on German industrialism, Undated (Box 13 (6-Miscellaneous Materials, Notes), Folder 18)
  - Linz, Juan. Book notes, Undated (Box 14 (6-Miscellaneous Materials, Notes), Folder 1)
  - Max Weber, Undated (Box 14 (6-Miscellaneous Materials, Notes), Folder 2)
  - Party Activists in East Germany, 1953-1954 (Box 14 (6-Miscellaneous Materials, Notes), Folder 3)
  - Schran, Peter. Materials on German entrepreneurs, Undated (Box 14 (6-Miscellaneous Materials, Notes), Folder 4)
  - Universities in Crisis, 1960s; clippings (Box 14 (6-Miscellaneous Materials, Notes), Folder 5)
  - University of California, Berkeley. Study Commission on University Governance, 1967-1968 (Box 14 (6-Miscellaneous Materials, Notes), Folder 6)
  - University of California, Berkeley. Committee on Rights to Intellectual Property, 1981-1982 (Box 14 (6-Miscellaneous Materials, Notes), Folder 7)
  - Miscellaneous publications, Undated (Box 14 (6-Miscellaneous Materials, Notes), Folder 8)
- Pamphlet Collection, 7; 55 file folders
  - Education for War: How a year of war has affected the American college and what more may happen, 1942 (Box 14 (7-Pamphlet Collection), Folder 9)
  - Ferment in Education: How and toward what shall we train American youth? First in a series on U.S. education, 1943 (Box 14 (7-Pamphlet Collection), Folder 10)
  - Problems and Opportunities of the Large University. Proceedings of the University of California Fifth All-University Faculty Conference. Davis Campus, April 27, 28, 29, 1950, Undated (Box 14 (7-Pamphlet Collection), Folder 11)
  - Understanding the Communists. Four Essays for the Liberal-Minded from Commentary, 1952 March (Box 14 (7-Pamphlet Collection), Folder 12)
  - The University as It Enters Its Second Century. Proceedings of the University of California Twenty-third All-University Faculty Conference. March 19-21, 1968, Undated (Box 14 (7-Pamphlet Collection), Folder 13)
  - Abrams, Frank W.The State of Business in American Education, Undated (Box 14 (7-Pamphlet Collection), Folder 14)
  - The All-Campus Committee Opposing the Broyles Bills and the Broyles Investigation. The Great Investigation, 1949 (Box 14 (7-Pamphlet Collection), Folder 15)
  - Almond, Gabriel A.How Many Anti-Nazi Germans?, 1946 (Box 14 (7-Pamphlet Collection), Folder 16)
  - Alumni Associations of the University of California.To Bring You the Facts..., 1950 August (Box 14 (7-Pamphlet Collection), Folder 17)
  - American Association for a Democratic Germany.A Program for a Democratic Germany, 1944 (Box 14 (7-Pamphlet Collection), Folder 18)
  - American Association for a Democratic Germany.They Fought Hitler First, 1945 May (Box 14 (7-Pamphlet Collection), Folder 19)
  - Blunschy-Steiner, Elisabeth.The Role of Swiss Women in Politics, 1971 July (Box 14 (7-Pamphlet Collection), Folder 20)
  - Brooks, Harvey.Can Science Be Planned?, 1967 (Box 14 (7-Pamphlet Collection), Folder 21)
  - Carnegie Corporation of New York.Are Graduate Schools Slighting a Major Function?, 1960 January (Box 14 (7-Pamphlet Collection), Folder 22)
  - Carnegie Corporation of New York.The Benevolent Despotism of Academia, Spring 1968 (Box 14 (7-Pamphlet Collection), Folder 23)
  - The Carnegie Foundation for the Advancement of Teaching.The University at the Service of Society, 1967 July (Box 14 (7-Pamphlet Collection), Folder 24)
  - Committee on Psychiatry in Industry of the Group for the Advancement of Psychiatry.The Application of Psychiatry to Industry, 1951 July (Box 14 (7-Pamphlet Collection), Folder 25)
  - Committee on Social Issues of the Group for the Advancement of Psychiatry.The Social Responsibility of Psychiatry. A Statement of Orientation, 1950 July (Box 14 (7-Pamphlet Collection), Folder 26)
  - Common Cause.Open Up the System. A Common Cause Manual for the 1972 Congressional Elections, 1972 October (Box 14 (7-Pamphlet Collection), Folder 27)